{
    "subject": "resource/Gazankulu",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Giyani",
    "human_readable": "Giyani is the capital of Gazankulu.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8656516671180725,
            "question": "What is the capital of Gazankulu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8218228220939636,
            "question": "Is Giyani a capital city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5139167308807373,
            "question": "Where is Giyani located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3342015743255615,
            "question": "What is the significance of Giyani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32718077301979065,
            "question": "Are there any notable landmarks or attractions in Giyani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29896068572998047,
            "question": "What is the population of Giyani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29840394854545593,
            "question": "Which province or region does Gazankulu belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26279059052467346,
            "question": "What are some cultural traditions associated with Giyani?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21833640336990356,
            "question": "How has Giyani evolved over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13391244411468506,
            "question": "What are the main industries or economic activities in Giyani?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Giyani is the capital of Gazankulu.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8774_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has Giyani evolved over time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8774_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some cultural traditions associated with Giyani?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8774_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which province or region does Gazankulu belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8774_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8774_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8774_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8774_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8774_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8774_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8774_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8774_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8774_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8774_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8774_63.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\nThe document with file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8774/re-ranker-msmarco/1.txt explicitly states that Giyani is a former capital of the then Gazankulu district. This supports the triple statement that Giyani is the capital of Gazankulu, although with the caveat that it was a former capital."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Giyani was once the capital town of the Gazankulu Bantustan government, and it also refers to Giyani as the former capital of Gazankulu. Thus, the statement \"Giyani is the capital of Gazankulu\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}